<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fiction on My recent posts:</title>
    <link>https://epic-knuth-170a38.netlify.com/tags/fiction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fiction on My recent posts:</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <managingEditor>sabtain.a.khan@gmail.com (Sabtain Khan)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>sabtain.a.khan@gmail.com (Sabtain Khan)</webMaster>
    <copyright>(c) 2019 Sabtain Khan.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://epic-knuth-170a38.netlify.com/tags/fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: David Copperfield</title>
      <link>https://epic-knuth-170a38.netlify.com/david-copperfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>sabtain.a.khan@gmail.com (Sabtain Khan)</author>
      <guid>https://epic-knuth-170a38.netlify.com/david-copperfield/</guid>
      <description>David Copperfield by Charles Dickens My rating: 5 of 5 stars
This is one of the few novels that I felt complete at its finish. Yes, parts of it are slow, but if you pay attention, and think deeply about the characters and how everything plays out chapter by chapter&amp;hellip;. you will get entranced in the beautiful Dickensian language and the plots eventually embodying the protagonist, David Copperfield.
The novel is about David Copperfield, and his coming-of-age&amp;hellip; It features everything, from childhood abuse and trauma, schooling, loss, friendship, family, love, marriage, business, villains etc&amp;hellip; Alogn the way, it helped me realize that things CAN be alright, and with time, patience and perseverance, I could overcome many obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Library at Mount Char</title>
      <link>https://epic-knuth-170a38.netlify.com/the-library-at-mount-char/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>sabtain.a.khan@gmail.com (Sabtain Khan)</author>
      <guid>https://epic-knuth-170a38.netlify.com/the-library-at-mount-char/</guid>
      <description>The Library at Mount Char by Scott Hawkins My rating: 3 of 5 stars
This book opens up very strong, and the characters and their mysterious origins and powers are quite interesting. The central plot is about 12 adopted siblings with special unique powers, working together to go back to their home, the mysterious &amp;lsquo;Library&amp;rsquo;. Along the way you learn about their powers and how they came to be, as well as their adopted &amp;lsquo;Father&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>